we2gather.com 2010-01-04

# WE2GATHER |

WETOGETHER was developed by principles of providing opportunities to people to discover new information by enabling them to share the best views which they find interesting with one another. WETOGETHER knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the WETOGETHER website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy .

This Privacy Policy covers WETOGETHER's management of personal information that WETOGETHER gathers when you are on the WETOGETHER website and when you use WETOGETHER services. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that WETOGETHER does not own or control, or to individuals that WETOGETHER does not employ or manage. 

We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website, which is to enable users to discover and share information with one another. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with this objective. We collect the following types of information from our WETOGETHER users: 

  1. Information You Provide to Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. 
  
<> Registration: In order for you to use WETOGETHER services, such as submitting new links to the website, you must complete a registration form. As part of this registration form, we require select personal information (including your full name, city, state and e-mail address). 

<> User Profile: To allow you to express yourself beyond just the information collected during registration, we enable you to provide additional information, such as a bio, favorite URLs, and instant messaging IDs. In addition, you may choose to include photos of yourself in your profile. As indicated below, in the section titled "Sharing Your Information", you can control how your information is displayed and used. 

  2. Automatic Information: 
  
<> We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. WETOGETHER and its authorized agents automatically receive and record certain "traffic data" on their server logs from your browser including your IP address, WETOGETHER cookie information, and the page you requested. WETOGETHER uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website. 

<> WETOGETHER may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page has been viewed. This includes User Profile pages. 

<> Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously. While WETOGETHER will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available. 

## E-mail Communications 

WETOGETHER is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission, as detailed in the "Sharing Your Information" section below. WETOGETHER may send out e-mails with WETOGETHER-related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions. You may also receive notification e-mails from WETOGETHER, which inform you of actions that have been performed on the site. 

## Cookies 

<> Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. WETOGETHER cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or e-mail address is. 

<> The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated because cookies allow you to use some of WETOGETHER's coolest features. 

<> Some of our business partners, like our advertisers, may use cookies on our website. We have no access to, or control over, these cookies. 

## Sharing Your Information

Because WETOGETHER enables people to discover and share information with one another, information about the people who use WETOGETHER is an integral part of the WETOGETHER experience. Rest assured that we neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone and that we will share your personal information only as described below. 

<> WETOGETHER Personnel: WETOGETHER personnel and authorized consultants and/or contractors may have access to user information if necessary in the normal course of WETOGETHER business. 

<> Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if WETOGETHER, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred. 

<> Protection of WETOGETHER and Others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other policies; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of WETOGETHER, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

<> User Profile information: Information collected during registration and subsequent visits, such as your full name and location, may be displayed to other WETOGETHER users in your User Profile. The User Profile is the area on WETOGETHER where we allow you to tell other WETOGETHER users about yourself and your interests. 

<> Member Directory: The e-mail address that you submit upon registration will be searchable by other WETOGETHER users who know you by your email address, unless you choose to opt out of this feature. This is primarily so that other users can find you to establish friendship through WETOGETHER. 

<> Social sharing of data: WETOGETHER allows other users to browse stories that you have gathered, submitted, saved, or commented on. This information is made available via your User Profile, on the WETOGETHER live page (http://www.we2gather.com/live.php) within the permalink URL of the story on which you performed the action. WETOGETHER may choose to post this data on other site features. 

<> Friends' Activity: Much like other online social networks, WETOGETHER allows non-friends to browse your friends' activity (www.we2gather.com/users/usersname/friends). 

<> Syndication: WETOGETHER allows for the RSS syndication of all of its public content within the WETOGETHER website. 

<> With Your Consent: Except as noted above, we will contact you when your personal information is shared with third parties or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, and you will be able to opt out to prevent the sharing of this information.
